Until one day, he kills
the wrong fucking people.
My people.
Relax.
I'm retrieving something
from my utility bag.
It's a goddamn fanny pack...
and you know it, you
sick son of a bitch!
The difference is night and day.
You remind me of my wife.
I'm sorry.
I said, "You remind
me of my wife."
No, I'm sorry that
you said that...
while making heavy eye contact
and applying lip balm.
She always struggled.
But she was funny...
and filtered her pain
through the prism of humor.
Something I could never master.
It was my fault she died.
It was my job to stop
people like him.
I came close a few times.
He wasn't too happy about that.
He was trying to hurt me...
and he knew exactly
how to do it.
Blessed are the wicked
who are healed by my hand.
He came into my home...
and took the only thing
that made it a home.
Sound familiar?
I'm sorry.Uh-huh.
No, I'm really sorry.
But that isn't Russell.
It doesn't have to be him.
If you knew what I knew...
Yeah, he's got anger issues...
maybe a small learning
disability...
splash of diabetes...
but nothing that can't be fixed.
If you could go back...
and stop the people that
took your girl, would you?
No.
I'd buy them all a
bouquet of hand jobs.
Of course I fucking would!
But I wouldn't kill a kid.
I'm not asking you
to kill a kid!
I'll kill the kid.
I'm asking you to save
hundreds of other kids.
Russell's gonna burn
down that orphanage.
And I can imagine your
dead girlfriend...
would want you to do the
right thing, wouldn't she?
So, what's it gonna
be, handsome?
Give me a chance to save him.
What? You said...
once he kills someone,
he gets a taste for it.
If we can get to him
before that happens...
promise you'll give me a chance
to put him on a different path.
Define "chance."
I don't know. How
long does it take
to save someone's soul?
That's not...
I'll give you 30 seconds.
What? No! Best I can do.
Take it or leave it.
He's doing it!
Look at the little fella.
He's doing it.
There he goes.
Jesus Christ!
Just shirt-cocking it.
Ugh.
There you go, little fella.
Go on, you're doing it!
My beautiful, hairless,
Twizzler-legged baby boy.
Christ!
That's disturbing.
30 seconds.
Deal.Deal.
Man, that sucks they didn't
have anything in your size.
I really wanted to
match, you know?
Being a menacing team.
Oh, man, it sucks.
That was some
cold-ass shit, kid.
And that is just the
first five steps
to a prostate-assisted orgasm.
Where the hell are we going?
You said it yourself.
Nothing can stop the Juggernaut.
We need backup.
I will bathe in the
blood of your enemies.
Can you turn off the music?
You'll do no such thing.
Why don't you just say
it in an Indian accent?
I'm sorry? Apology accepted.
This is a side of
you I do not like.
Let me guess,
some of your best friends
in the future are Indian.
What the hell are you...?
Once again, intolerance
rears its ugly head.
I am so sorry. It gets better.
I'm not a fucking racist, moron!
That's precisely what
a racist would say.
I'm with the old white
guy on this one.
And that's a twist.
When this is over...
I'm going to fuck you to death
with your own broken feet.
And a sexual predator, too.
That's rich.
I should have finished college.
So what exactly do you
do in the future, anyway, huh?
Some kind of soldier?
Yeah, something like that.
I was a soldier. Special Forces.
I bet 50 years from now,
we're bestest buddies.
50 years from now,
you're very dead.
Your entire generation fucked
this planet into a coma.
Boom!
Spoiler alert.
Planets.
Next time, Uber.
Here's a spoiler alert.
You're not a fucking hero.
You're just an annoying clown
dressed up as a sex toy.
Well, I got news for you.
My heart is in the right place.
Russell's not gonna kill anyone.
Because of me, he's gonna know
what real love looks like.
We're all going to die.
Because of you, I'll always know
what a grown man with
baby balls looks like.
I'm a grower, not a shower.
God, I wish this were a bus
where I could pull the
string and get out.
It's a good thing
Cable's not driving,
or you'd be in the back.
I am in the back.
DEADPOOL: Right here!
I made mistakes!
I wanna take them back!
You trusted me. I
took that trust...
and turned it into a glory hole
in an airport bathroom.
The one in Minneapolis.
You know the one.
But even you know I'm not
a complete piece of shit.
I was once an X-Man.
Trainee!
You're still using my
Velcro labels. Aw.
They do stick better than tape.
Hi, Wade!
Please don't.
Say whatever it is you're here to say.
Make it quick.
Right. Quick.
It's the kid. Just like
you, I let him down.
And just like me,
he's never had anyone
sacrifice anything for him...
because the whole
world wrote him off
as a piece of shit
a long time ago.
Look, he's teamed up
with the Juggernaut!
The Juggernaut!
Who's, like, my favorite
Marvel character ever...
And hi, Yukio! That was really
nice of you to say hi...
so I'm saying hi back.
You guys make a
super cute couple.
Yeah. Where was I?
Oh, yeah. You should never
meet your heroes...
because, honestly,
he's a bit of a dick!
And like a lot of dicks,
he's hard as a rock...
and causes nothing but problems!
Look, you can stop the Juggernaut.
I know you can.
Do you know what would happen
to me if I helped you?
I would be disgraced.
You are a criminal, a fugitive.
But worst of all...
you broke my heart, Wade.
Then you know what?
Your heart's in the
wrong place, big guy.
Doing the right thing
is sometimes messy...
and fucked up, and not
particularly convenient!
So stay here in
Chateau de Virgin...
while we go get our fuck on!
You're doing great.
So you wear that helmet because
your brother tries
to read your mind?
Yeah, but he's in a
wheelchair, so even-steven.
Someone's coming.
It's Russell, sir.
And he's not alone.
Secure the children.
They will not replace us.
What do you say we go
fuck some shit up?
"Let's fuck some shit up"
is my legal middle name.
Watch my back. I've
got the old man.
Amen, brother.
Time to make the chimichangas.
30 seconds.
I finally know why I'm here.
I was raised in this place.
Well, not raised.
I was tortured.
Wow! It's your cosmic
reason for being here.
Shall we? This is gonna be fun.
Yeah!
Hey! Been meaning to ask you...
what's with the dirty,
disgusting hobo bear?
It's not dirt. It's the
blood of my dead daughter.
Are You Bear, God?
It's Me, Margaret.
Give me some.
They say laughter
heals anything...
except, of course, that.
We should just cue the music.
Welcome home, Russell.
We missed you.
Russell!
You don't need to do this!
Let's talk!
Why are you dressed
like the Unabomber?
That's why!
Told you this little
fucker's too far gone.
Zip it, Thanos! We have
a deal and you fuck...
Hey!
I'm gonna shove that cab
driver right up your ass.
My body and my
hands are so soft.
You should probably
head back to the car.
I think I'll head
back to the car.
It works best when you
pull the trigger.
That gun is amazing!
Say it!
You are an abomination!
Now, I'm gonna shove the
red guy up the old guy.
I believe him! Every
man for themselves!
Gotcha!
Beat it, midget!
Hey, big guy, the sun's
getting real low!
Oh, shit fuck!
Come here, beautiful.
Whoo!
Say it!
You came for me.
I'm not giving up on you,
and you are not giving
up on that boy.
Who says that rules aren't
meant to be broken?
It's time to fight dirty.
Time to sweep the leg, Johnny.
Hey! Pick on someone
your own size!
That's such a you thing to say!
Go get him, tiger!
Big CGI fight coming up!
He's doing great.
Say it!
Russell. DEADPOOL: Bingo!
You see that bus?
I'm gonna shove it up your ass.
That's right! I'm
fighting dirty!
Oh, great!
There they are! Those freaks!
A bunch of armed pedophiles
in nursing shoes.
Can I have one of those guns?
No.That's fine.
Get off this property,
mutant scum!
I'm just gonna use this brick.
Maximum effort.